amateurcreampies.com 2018-12-18

# Amateur Creampies - Amateur cum sluts getting their pussies filled with sperm

**An Overview**

Pacific Century Int  is fully committed to protecting the privacy of consumers of its interactive products and services. We want to contribute to providing a safe and secure environment for everyone, and in particular, ensure that our members' personal information is protected. 

This privacy policy extends to all Pacific Century Int  operated sites including all of our Internet-accessible Pacific Century Int  branded services, hereafter called simply "Pacific Century Int ". This Privacy Policy is to inform you, as a welcome visitor to the world of Pacific Century Int , what kinds of information we may gather about you when you visit; how we may use that information; whether we disclose it to anyone, and the choices you have regarding our use of, and your ability to correct, the information we hold. 

Finally, please note that this policy applies only to Pacific Century Int  built and maintained Web sites that carry the Pacific Century Int  brand, and not to any other company or organizations' Web sites to which we link or have affiliated to. We have clearly marked Pacific Century Int  and these branded Web sites with our logo so you know where this policy applies. 

**Information about all Pacific Century Int   visitors that Pacific Century Int  automatically receives from you **

In general, our service automatically gathers certain usage information like the numbers and frequency of visitors, very much like television ratings that tell the networks how many people tuned in to a program. We only use such data in the aggregate. This collective data helps us determine how much our customers use parts of a given site. This allows us to improve our services and ensure that they are as appealing as they can be. For example, Pacific Century Int  uses a technology nicknamed "cookies" that tells us how and when pages in our site are visited, and by how many people. Such cookies do not collect personally identifiable information and we do not combine information collected through cookies with other personally identifiable information to tell us who you are or even what your screen name or e-mail address is. 

We also may provide statistical "ratings" information, never information about you personally, to our partners and affiliates about how our members (collectively) use our services. We do this so they too can understand how much people use their areas and our site in order for them to provide you with the best possible Web experience. 

Information about you that you provide us 

Sometimes, we may specifically ask for information about you when you sign up to use a service, join a members' only area, or when you order a product. We will need certain information, for example, name, Internet address or screen name, billing address, credit card number, or any other relevant information as may be required by our Credit Card (or other payment method) Processors to ensure that the transaction is genuine or that your right to access a site is of a bone fide nature. This is for our users protection as well as for our own. 

We may also use that information to let you know of additional products and services that we believe would be of interest to you. You may choose not to receive such information if you don't want to by letting us know on the registration screen when you sign up for that product or service, or by emailing via the link that can be found on the site that you have joined.   
We may also ask you for information about your interests so that both you and we can take advantage of the interactivity of the online medium that is the Internet, but you may always choose to respond or not. 

Additionally, we may provide you with an opportunity to be listed in a directory on one of our Pacific Century Int  branded services and these listings are also optional and you can make changes to or eliminate this information whenever you want to. 

**Disclosure**

We do not use or disclose information about your individual visits to any Pacific Century Int  operated site or any information that you may give us, such as your name, address, Email address or telephone number, to any outside company or organization unless we are legally requested to do so as part of any Federal Investigation or to protect or enforce our own legal rights under any agreement which has been breached, or we believe has been breached, or to protect any and all copyright infringements. In such events Pacific Century Int  shall only release information when Pacific Century Int  believe it appropriate to and then only to the relevant authority. 

It is your obligation to provide Pacific Century Int  with accurate and up-to-date information, and failure to provide us with such information could void any Agreement between you and Pacific Century Int . We use the information that you provide for such purposes as processing your purchase request, responding to customer service inquiries, loss prevention, improving our service, communicating with you, and allowing our billing providers to provide customer service and thus fulfil their obligations to you. Pacific Century Int  employees and associated site webmasters and copyright holders have access to your information on a need-to-know but fully secured basis. Pacific Century Int  will not sell your information to a third party for any reason. 

Pacific Century Int  does not request, or knowingly collect identifiable information from children under the age of 18. Pacific Century Int  does not knowingly use or share personal information from users under the age of 18 with third parties. Pacific Century Int  does not offer children any promotions involving games, prizes, or any other activity that would induce a child to divulge personal information. 

**Data Protection**

Pacific Century Int  and its associated websites employ the latest and best techniques available for protecting its systems from intrusion by unauthorized individuals, and both we and our associated webmasters and billing providers are constantly upgrading security as better methods become available. All information is stored behind firewalls and other sophisticated security systems. All data centres housing hardware utilise state-of-the-art physical security measures to prevent unauthorized access to any facility. 

**Paycom, CCBill and 2000 Charge acting as Agents for Pacific Century Int**

Pacific Century Int  use Ibill, CCBill and 2000 Charge as resellers of the Pacific Century Int  product for Credit Cards, Web900 and/or Online Check payment facilities. Consumers utilising such options shall be bound by the Terms and Conditions; Billing Policies and Privacy Statements for Pacific Century Int  as well as Ibill and/or Jettis. You may read information and find links for all of Policies by visiting: 

Paycom - [http://www. paycom.net ](http://www.ibill.com/Disclaimer.html)

CCBill - [https://www.ccbill.com/system/privacy.htm ](https://www.ccbill.com/system/privacy.htm)

2000 Charge - [http://www.2000Charge.com/ ](http://billingservices.com/)

**Pacific Century Int   Privacy Policy Changes **

If we decide to change our privacy policy for Pacific Century Int , we will post those changes here so that you will always know what information we gather, how we might use that information and whether we will disclose it to anyone. As a user of our services you may therefore have complete faith and confidence in all your dealings with us. By registering our data and having it independently audited we wish to demonstrate our commitment to your privacy. ****
